100£2£1£Arvel Crynyd£6£You may declare an enemy ship inside your firing arc that you are touching as the target of your attack.£5£23££2
101£2£1£Gemmer Sojan£5£While you are at Range 1 of at least 1 enemy ship, increase your agility value by 1.£5£22££2
102£2£0£Green Squadron Pilot£3£Conceived by General Dodonna, the RZ-1 A-wing interceptor proved its worth by crippling Star Destroyers during the Battle of Endor.£2,5£19££2
103£2£1£Jake Farrell£7£After you perform a focus action or are assigned a focus token, you may perform a free boost or barrel roll action.£2,5£24££2
104£2£0£Prototype Pilot£1£Due to its sensitive controls and high maneuverability, only the most talented pilots belong in an A-wing cockpit.£5£17££2
105£2£1£Tycho Celchu£8£You may perform actions even while you have stress tokens.£2,5£26££2
200£5£0£Blue Squadron Pilot£2£Because of its heavy weapons array and resilient shielding, the B-wing solidified itself as the Alliance's most formidable assault fighter.£11,6,4,4£22££2
201£5£0£Dagger Squadron Pilot£4£A unique gyrostabilization surrounds the B-Wing's cockpit, ensuring that the pilot always remains stationary during combat.£11,6,4,4£24££2
202£5£1£Ibtisam£6£When attacking or defending, if you have at least one stress token, you may reroll 1 of your dice.£2,11,6,4,4£28££2
203£5£1£Keyan Farlander£7£When attacking, you may remove 1 stress token to change all of your focus results to hit results.£2,11,6,4,4£29££2
204£5£1£Nera Dantels£5£You can perform Torpedoes secondary weapon attacks against enemy ships outside your firing arc.£2,11,6,4,4£26££2
205£5£1£Ten Numb£8£When attacking, 1 of your critical results cannot be canceled by defense dice.£11,6,4,4£31££2
300£7£0£Blackmoon Squadron Pilot£3£Originally designed with only the R7-series of astromech in mind, the E-wing was later retrofitted to equip the standard R2- and R5-series droids.£11,4,3£29££2
301£7£1£Corran Horn£8£At the start of the End phase, you may perform one attack. You cannot attack during the next round.£2,11,4,3£35££2
302£7£1£Etahn A'baht£5£When an enemy ship inside your firing arc at Range 1-3 is defending, the attacker may change 1 of its hit results to a critical result.£2,11,4,3£32££2
303£7£0£Knave Squadron Pilot£1£Specifically designed to combine the best features of the X-wing series with the A-wing series, the E-wing boasted superior firepower, speed, and maneuverability.£11,4,3£27££2
400£13£1£Jan Ors£8£When another friendly ship at Range 1-3 is attacking, if you have no stress tokens, you may receive 1 stress token to allow that ship to roll 1 additional attack die.£2,7,9£25££2
401£13£1£Kyle Katarn£6£At the start of the Combat phase, you may assign 1 of your focus tokens to another friendly ship at Range 1-3.£2,7,9£21££2
402£13£1£Roark Garnet£4£At the start of the Combat phase, choose 1 other friendly ship at Range 1-3. Until the end of the phase, treat that ship's pilot skill value as "12".£7,9£19££2
403£13£0£Rebel Operative£2£Designed after a bird in flight by Corellian Engineering Corporation, the "hawk" series excels in its role as a personal transport.£7,9£16££2
500£18£1£Esege Tuketu£6£When another friendly ship at Range 1-2 is attacking, it may treat your focus tokens as its own.£7,4,4,5,9,8,8£28££2
501£18£0£Guardian Squadron Pilot£4£The K-wing’s surprising acceleration, heavy armor plating, and devastating ordnance made it a favorite for hit-and-run operations.£7,4,4,5,9,8,8£25££2
502£18£1£Miranda Doni£8£Once per round when attacking, you may either spend 1 shield to roll 1 additional attack die or roll 1 fewer attack die to recover 1 shield.£7,4,4,5,9,8,8£29££2
503£18£0£Warden Squadron Pilot£2£Koensayr Manufacturing's K-Wing boasted an advanced Sublight Acceleration Motor (SLAM) and an uprecedented 18 hard points, granting it unrivaled speed and firepower.£7,4,4,5,9,8,8£23££2
600£25£1£"Blue Ace"£5£When performing a boost action, you may use the [1 left] or [1 right] turn template.£4,3,18£27££2
601£25£1£"Red Ace"£6£The first time you remove a shield token from your ship each round, assign 1 evade token to your ship.£4,3,18£29££2
602£25£0£Blue Squadron Novice£2£The T-70 model benefits from its redesigned thrusters with increased maneuverability in both space and atmospheric flight.£4,3,18£24££2
603£25£1£Ello Asty£7£While you are not stressed, you may treat your [Talon Roll Left] and [Talon Roll Right] maneuvers as white maneuvers.£2,4,3,18£30££2
604£25£1£Poe Dameron£8£While attacking or defending, if you have a focus token, you may change 1 of your focus results to a hit or evade result.£2,4,3,18£31££2
605£25£0£Red Squadron Veteran£4£The modern incarnation of a classic design, the Incom T-70 X-wing fighter is the signature combat craft of the Resistance forces in their fight against the First Order.£4,3,18£26££2
606£25£1£Poe Dameron£9£While attacking or defending, if you have a focus token, you may change 1 of your focus results to a hit or evade result.£2,4,3,18£33££2
700£37£1£"Hobbie" Klivian£5£When you acquire or spend a target lock, you may remove 1 stress token from your ship.£4,3£25££2
701£37£1£Biggs Darklighter£5£Other friendly ships at Range 1 cannot be targeted by attacks if the attacker could target you instead.£4,3£25££2
702£37£1£Garven Dreis£6£After spending a focus token, you may place that token on any other friendly ship at Range 1-2 (instead of discarding it).£4,3£26££2
703£37£1£Jek Porkins£7£When you receive a stress token, you may remove it and roll 1 attack die. On a hit result, deal 1 facedown Damage card to this ship.£2,4,3£26££2
704£37£1£Luke Skywalker£8£When defending, you may change 1 of your focus results to an evade result.£2,4,3£28££2
705£37£0£Red Squadron Pilot£4£Created as an elite starfighter squad, Red Squadron included some of the best pilots in the Rebel Alliance.£4,3£23££2
706£37£0£Rookie Pilot£2£Designed by Incom Corporation, the T-65 X-Wing quickly proved to be one of the most effective military vehicles in the galaxy and a boon to the Rebellion.£4,3£21££2
707£37£1£Tarn Mison£3£When an enemy ship declares you as the target of an attack, you may acquire a target lock on that ship.£4,3£23££2
708£37£1£Wedge Antilles£9£When attacking, reduce the defender's agility value by 1 (to a minimum of "0").£2,4,3£29££2
709£37£1£Wes Janson£8£After you perform an attack, you may remove 1 focus, evade, or blue target lock token from the defender.£2,4,3£29££2
800£38£1£"Dutch" Vander£6£After acquiring a target lock, choose another friendly ship at Range 1-2. The chosen ship may immediately acquire a target lock.£7,4,4,3£23££2
801£38£0£Gold Squadron Pilot£2£The versatile and reliable BTL-A4 Y-wing was the Rebellion's primary starfighter until the arrival of the T-65 X-wing.£7,4,4,3£18££2
802£38£0£Gray Squadron Pilot£4£Long after the Y-wing was to be phased out, its speed, durability and weapon options helped it remain a staple in the Rebel fleet.£7,4,4,3£20££2
803£38£1£Horton Salm£8£When attacking at Range 2-3, you may reroll any of your blank results.£7,4,4,3£25££2
900£39£1£Chewbacca£5£When you are dealt a faceup Damage card, immediately flip it facedown (without resolving its ability).£2,5,9,9£42££2
901£39£1£Han Solo£9£When attacking, you may reroll all of your dice. If you choose to do so, you must reroll as many of your dice as possible.£2,5,9,9£46££2
902£39£1£Lando Calrissian£7£After you execute a green maneuver, choose 1 other friendly ship at Range 1. That ship may perform 1 free action shown in its action bar.£2,5,9,9£44££2
903£39£0£Outer Rim Smuggler£1£Known for its durability and modular design, the YT-1300 is one of the most popular, widely used freighters in the galaxy.£9,9£27££2
904£39£1£Han Solo£9£When you are placed during setup, you can be placed anywhere in the play area beyond Range 3 of the enemy ships.£2,5,9,9£46££2
905£39£1£Rey£8£When attacking or defending, if the enemy ship is inside your firing arc, you may reroll up to 2 of your blank results.£2,5,9,9£45££2
906£39£1£Chewbacca£5£When another friendly ship at Range 1-3 is destroyed (but has not fled the battlefield), you may perform an attack.£2,5,9,9£42££2
907£39£0£Resistance Sympathizer£3£After the destruction of the Hosnian system, some spacers willingly aided the Resistance against the malevolent First Order.£5,9,9£38££2
1000£40£1£"Leebo"£5£When you are dealt a faceup Damage card, draw 1 additional Damage card, choose 1 to resolve, and discard the other.£2,6,5,9£34££2
1001£40£1£Dash Rendar£7£You may ignore obstacles during the Activation phase and when performing actions.£2,6,5,9£36££2
1002£40£1£Eaden Vrill£3£When performing a primary weapon attack against a stressed ship, roll 1 additional attack die.£6,5,9£32££2
1003£40£0£Wild Space Fringer£2£Although a stock YT-2400 light freighter had plenty of space for cargo, that space was often annexed to support modified weapon systems and oversized engines.£6,5,9£30££2
1100£42£1£Airen Cracken£8£After you perform an attack, you may choose another friendly ship at Range 1. That ship may perform 1 free action.£2,5£19££2
1101£42£1£Lieutenant Blount£6£When attacking, the defender is hit by your attack, even if he does not suffer any damage.£2,5£17££2
1102£42£0£Tala Squadron Pilot£4£Manufactured by Incom Corporation, the Z-95-AF4 was the primary inspiration for the design of the T-65 X-wing.£5£13££2
1103£42£0£Bandit Squadron Pilot£2£The AF4 series was the latest in a long line of Headhunter designs. Cheap and durable, it became a favorite among independent outfits like the Rebellion and Black Sun.£5£12££2
1200£8£1£Boba Fett£8£When you reveal a bank maneuver (Left Bank or Right Bank), you may rotate your dial to the other bank maneuver of the same speed.£2,6,8,9,5£39££3
1201£8£0£Bounty Hunter£3£Originally intended as a prisoner transport, the Firespray patrol craft features a versatile weapons array and heavy armor plating.£6,8,9,5£33££3
1202£8£1£Kath Scarlet£7£When attacking, the defender receives 1 stress token if he cancels at least 1 critical result.£2,6,8,9,5£38££3
1203£8£1£Krassis Trelix£5£When attacking with a secondary weapon, you may reroll 1 attack die.£6,8,9,5£36££3
1300£32£0£"Redline"£7£You may maintain 2 target locks on the same ship. When you acquire a target lock, you may acquire a second lock on that same ship.£11,4,4,5,5,8,8£27££3
1301£32£0£"Deathrain"£6£When dropping a bomb, you may use the front guides of your ship. After dropping a bomb, you may perform a free barrel roll action.£11,4,4,5,5,8,8£26££3
1302£32£0£Black Eight Sq. Pilot£4£Darth Vader's hand-picked Black Eight Squadron earned its reputation for ruthlessness when its bombardment of Callos rendered the planet uninhabitable.£11,4,4,5,5,8,8£23££3
1303£32£0£Cutlass Squadron Pilot£2£The TIE Punisher built upon the success of the TIE bomber, adding shielding, a second bomb chute, and three additional ordnance pods, each equipped with a twin ion engine.£11,4,4,5,5,8,8£21££3
1400£20£1£Captain Kagi£8£When an enemy ship acquires a target lock, it must lock onto your ship if able.£11,6,9,9£27££3
1401£20£1£Captain Yorr£4£When another friendly ship at Range 1-2 would receive a stress token, if you have 2 or fewer stress tokens, you may receive that token instead.£11,6,9,9£24££3
1402£20£1£Colonel Jendon£6£At the start of the Combat phase, you may assign one of your blue target lock tokens to a friendly ship at Range 1 if it does not have a blue target lock token.£11,6,9,9£26££3
1403£20£0£Omicron Group Pilot£2£Noted for its tri-wing design, the Lambda-class shuttle served a critical role as a light utility craft in the Imperial Navy.£11,6,9,9£21££3
1500£26£1£Darth Vader£9£During your "Perform Action" step, you may perform 2 actions.£2,5£29££3
1501£26£1£Maarek Stele£7£When your attack deals a faceup Damage card to the defender, instead draw 3 Damage cards, choose 1 to deal and discard the others.£2,5£27££3
1502£26£1£Commander Alozen£5£At the start of the Combat phase, you may acquire a target lock on an enemy ship at Range 1.£2,5£25££3
1503£26£1£Juno Eclipse£8£When you reveal your maneuver, you may increase or decrease its speed by 1 (to a minimum of 1).£2,5£28££3
1504£26£1£Zertik Strom£6£Enemy ships at Range 1 cannot add their range combat bonus when attacking.£2,5£26££3
1505£26£1£Lieutenant Colzet£3£At the start of the End phase, you may spend a target lock you have on an enemy ship to flip 1 random facedown Damage card assigned to it faceup.£5£23££3
1506£26£0£Storm Squadron Pilot£4£The TIE Advanced improved on the popular TIE/ln design by adding shielding, better weapons systems, curved solar panels and a hyperdrive.£5£23££3
1507£26£0£Tempest Squadron Pilot£2£The TIE Advanced was produced in limited quantities, but later Sienar engineers incorporated many of its best qualities into their next TIE model: the TIE Interceptor.£5£21££3
1600£27£1£Captain Jonus£6£When another friendly ship at Range 1 attacks with a secondary weapon, it may reroll up to 2 attack dice.£2,4,4,5,5,8£22££3
1601£27£1£"Deathfire"£3£When you reveal your maneuver dial or after you perform an action, you may perform a Bomb Upgrade card action as a free action.£4,4,5,5,8£17££3
1602£27£0£Gamma Squadron Pilot£4£While not as agile or fast as other TIE variants, TIE bombers can carry enough firepower to destroy virtually any enemy target.£4,4,5,5,8£18££3
1603£27£0£Gamma Squadron Veteran£5£The white-striped TIE bombers flown by the elite Gamma Squadron possess enhanced maneuverability, allowing them to nimbly strike capital ships with fearsome ease.£2,4,4,5,5,8£18££3
1604£27£1£Major Rhymer£7£When attacking with a secondary weapon, you may increase or decrease the weapon range by 1 to a limit of Range 1-3.£2,4,4,5,5,8£26££3
1605£27£0£Scimitar Squadron Pilot£2£The onboard targeting computer is extremely precise, allowing a TIE bomber to pinpoint its target while avoiding collateral damage to the surrounding area.£4,4,5,5,8£16££3
1606£27£1£Tomax Bren£8£Once per round, after you discard an Elite Upgrade card, flip that card faceup.£2,4,4,5,5,8£24££3
1700£28£1£Colonel Vessery£6£When attacking, immediately after you roll attack dice, you may acquire a target lock on the defender if it already has a red target lock token.£2,6,5£35££3
1701£28£1£Countess Ryad£5£When you reveal a [Straight] maneuver, you may treat it as a [K-Turn] maneuver.£2,6,5£34££3
1702£28£0£Delta Squadron Pilot£1£In addition to its four laser cannons and warhead launchers, the TIE defender came equipped with ion cannons in its upper wing.£6,5£30££3
1703£28£1£Maarek Stele£7£When your attack deals a faceup Damage card to the defender, instead draw 3 Damage cards, choose 1 to deal and discard the others.£2,6,5£35££3
1704£28£0£Onyx Squadron Pilot£3£The TIE defender outclassed all other starfighters of its time, though its size and array of weapons greatly increased its weight and cost in credits.£6,5£32££3
1705£28£1£Rexler Brath£8£After you perform an attack that deals at least 1 Damage card to the defender, you may spend a focus token to flip those cards faceup.£2,6,5£37££3
1800£29£0£Academy Pilot£1£Developed by Sienar Fleet Systems, the Empire used the fast and agile TIE/ln as its primary starfighter throughout most of the Galactic Civil War.££12££3
1801£29£1£"Backstabber"£6£When attacking from outside the defender's firing arc, roll 1 additional attack die.££16££3
1802£29£0£Black Squadron Pilot£4£The TIE fighter has no shields or life support systems, forcing TIE pilots to depend solely on their skills to survive.£2£14££3
1803£29£1£"Chaser"£3£When another friendly ship at Range 1 spends a focus token, assign a focus token to your ship.££14££3
1804£29£1£"Dark Curse"£6£When defending, ships attacking you cannot spend focus tokens or reroll attack die.££16££3
1805£29£1£"Howlrunner"£8£When another friendly ship at Range 1 is attacking with its primary weapon, it may reroll 1 attack die.£2£18££3
1806£29£1£"Mauler Mithel"£7£When attacking at Range 1, roll 1 additional attack die.£2£17££3
1807£29£1£"Night Beast"£5£After executing a green maneuver, you may perform a free focus action.££15££3
1808£29£0£Obsidian Squadron Pilot£3£The TIE fighter's Twin Ion Engine system was designed for speed, making the TIE one of the most maneuverable starships ever produced.££13££3
1809£29£1£"Scourge"£7£When attacking a defender that has 1 or more Damage cards, roll 1 additional attack die.£2£17££3
1810£29£1£"Wampa"£4£When attacking, at the start of the "Compare Results" step, you may cancel all dice results. If you cancel a critical result, deal 1 facedown Damage card to the defender.££14££3
1811£29£1£"Winged Gundark"£5£When attacking at Range 1, you may change 1 of your hit results to a critical result.££15££3
1812£29£1£"Youngster"£6£Friendly TIE fighters at Range 1-3 may perform the action on your equipped Elite Talent Upgrade card.£2£15££3
1900£33£1£"Epsilon Leader"£6£At the start of the Combat phase, remove 1 stress token from each friendly ship at Range 1.£18£19££3
1901£33£0£Epsilon Squadron Pilot£1£Following the tradition of the Galactic Empire, the First Order has kept the TIE fighter design in service, but has updated the craft to modern combat standards.£18£15££3
1902£33£1£"Omega Ace"£7£When attacking, you may spend a focus token and a target lock you have on the defender to change all of your results to Critical Hit results.£2,18£20££3
1903£33£1£"Omega Leader"£8£Enemy ships that you have locked cannot modify any dice when attacking you or defending against your attacks.£2,18£21££3
1904£33£0£Omega Squadron Pilot£4£To attain a coveted position in the skilled Omega squadron, pilots had to demonstate both their exceptional skill and their unwavering dedication to the First Order.£2,18£17££3
1905£33£1£"Zeta Ace"£5£When performing a barrel roll, you may use the Straight 2 template (instead of the Straight 1 template).£2,18£18££3
1906£33£0£Zeta Squadron Pilot£3£The fragility of TIE fighters during the Galactic Civil War led engineers to improve survivability, resulting in a more durable starfighter.£18£16££3
2000£30£0£Alpha Squadron Pilot£1£Sienar Fleet Systems designed the TIE Interceptor with four wing-mounted laser cannons, easily allowing it to outgun its predecessors.££18££3
2001£30£0£Avenger Squadron Pilot£3£The finest mass-produced starfighter of its time, the TIE Interceptor excels at dogfighting thanks to its heightened maneuverability and speed.££20££3
2002£30£1£Carnor Jax£8£Enemy ships at Range 1 cannot perform focus or evade actions and cannot spend focus or evade tokens.£2£26££3
2003£30£1£"Fel's Wrath"£5£When the number of Damage cards assigned to you equals or exceeds your hull value, you are not destroyed until the end of the Combat phase.££23££3
2004£30£1£Kir Kanos£6£When attacking at Range 2 or 3, you may spend 1 evade token to add 1 hit result to your roll.££24££3
2005£30£1£Lieutenant Lorrir£5£When performing a barrel roll action, you may receive 1 stress token to use the [Bank Left 1] or [Bank Right 1] template instead of the [Straight 1] to roll.££23££3
2006£30£0£Royal Guard Pilot£6£Only members of the Emperor's royal guard are permitted to fly these crimson red fighters, which were often used to escort the Emperor's shuttle as well as its decoys.£2£22££3
2007£30£0£Saber Squadron Pilot£4£Led by Baron Soontir Fel, the pilots of Saber Squadron are among the Empire's best. Their TIE Interceptors are marked with red stripes to designate pilots with at least ten confirmed kills.£2£21££3
2008£30£1£Soontir Fel£9£When you receive a stress token, you may assign 1 focus token to your ship.£2£27££3
2009£30£1£Tetran Cowall£7£When you reveal a [Koiogran turn] maneuver, you may treat the speed of that maneuver as "1," "3," or "5."£2£24££3
2010£30£1£Turr Phennir£7£After you perform an attack, you may perform a free boost or barrel roll action.£2£25££3
2100£31£1£"Echo"£6£When you decloak, you must use the Left Bank 2 or Right Bank 2 template instead of the Straight 2 template.£2,11,9£30££3
2101£31£0£Shadow Squadron Pilot£5£Featuring a hyperdrive and shields, the TIE phantom also came equipped with five laser cannons, giving it unprecedented firepower for such a small Imperial fighter.£11,9£27££3
2102£31£0£Sigma Squadron Pilot£3£The primary result of a hidden research facility on Imdaar Alpha, the TIE phantom added a small fighter with cloaking capabilities to the Imperial fleet.£11,9£25££3
2103£31£1£"Whisper"£7£After you perform an attack that hits, you may assign 1 focus token to your ship.£2,11,9£32££3
2200£36£1£Captain Oicunn£4£After executing a maneuver, each enemy ship you are touching suffers 1 damage.£2,4,9,9,9,8£42££3
2201£36£1£Commander Kenkirk£6£If you have no shields and at least 1 Damage card assigned to you, increase your agility value by 1.£2,4,9,9,9,8£44££3
2202£36£0£Patrol Leader£3£To be granted command of a VT-49 Decimator was seen as a significant promotion for a middling officer of the Imperial Navy.£4,9,9,9,8£40££3
2203£36£1£Rear Admiral Chiraneau£8£When attacking at Range 1-2, you may change one of your focus results to a critical result.£2,4,9,9,9,8£46££3
2300£43£1£IG-88A£6£After you perform an attack that destroys the defender, you may recover 1 shield.£2,11,6,6,8,14£36££4
2301£43£1£IG-88B£6£Once per round, after you perform an attack that does not hit, you may perform an attack with an equipped Cannon secondary weapon.£2,11,6,6,8,14£36££4
2302£43£1£IG-88C£6£After you perform a boost action, you may perform a free evade action.£2,11,6,6,8,14£36££4
2303£43£1£IG-88D£6£You may execute the [3-Left Segnor's Loop] or [3-Right Segnor's Loop] maneuver using the corresponding [3-Left Turn] or [3-Right Turn] template.£2,11,6,6,8,14£36££4
2400£8£1£Emon Azzameen£6£When dropping a bomb, you may use a Left Turn 3, Straight 3, or Right Turn 3 template instead of the Straight 1 template.£6,8,9,5,14£36££4
2401£8£1£Boba Fett£8£When attacking or defending, you may reroll 1 of your dice for each enemy ship at Range 1.£2,6,8,9,5,14£39££4
2402£8£1£Kath Scarlet£7£When attacking a ship inside your auxiliary firing arc, roll 1 additional attack die.£2,6,8,9,5,14£38££4
2403£8£0£Mandalorian Mercenary£5£Though the Mandalorian Crusaders were all but destroyed by the Old Republic, a handful of enterprising mercenaries still claim the mantle, instilling terror in their foes.£2,6,8,9,5,14£35££4
2500£13£1£Dace Bonearm£7£When an enemy ship at Range 1-3 receives at least one ion token, if you are not stressed you may receive 1 stress token to cause that ship to suffer 1 damage.£2,7,9,14£23££4
2501£13£1£Palob Godalhi£5£At the start of the Combat phase, you may remove 1 focus or evade token from an enemy ship at Range 1-2 and assign it to yourself.£2,7,9,14£20££4
2502£13£0£Spice Runner£1£With nothing more than a desire to fly and a junkyard at their disposal, crafty mechanics can make almost anything space worthy.£7,9,14£16££4
2503£13£1£Torkil Mux£3£At the end of the Activation phase, choose 1 enemy ship at Range 1-2. Until the end of the Combat phase, treat that ship's pilot skill value as "0".£7,9,14£19££4
2600£19£0£Cartel Marauder£2£The versatile Kihraxz was modeled after Incom's popular X-wing starfighter, but an array of after-market modification kits ensured a wide variety of designs.£5,14£20££4
2601£19£0£Black Sun Ace£5£The Kihraxz assault fighter was developed specifically for the Black Sun crime syndicate, whose highly paid ace pilots demanded a nimble, powerful ship to match their skills.£2,5,14£23££4
2602£19£1£Graz The Hunter£6£When defending, if the attacker is inside your firing arc, roll 1 additional defense die.£5,14£25££4
2603£19£1£Talonbane Cobra£9£When attacking or defending, double the effect of your range combat bonuses.£2,5,14£28££4
2700£21£0£Cartel Spacer£2£MandalMotors' M3-A "Scyk" Interceptor was purchased in large quantities by the Hutt Cartel and the Car'das smugglers due to its low cost and customizability.££14££4
2701£21£0£Tansarii Point Veteran£5£The defeat of Black Sun ace Talonbane Cobra by Car'das smugglers turned the tide of the Battle of Tansarii Point Station. Survivor s of the clash are respected throughout the sector.£2£17££4
2702£21£1£Serissu£8£When another friendly ship at Range 1 is defending, it may reroll 1 defense die.£2£20££4
2703£21£1£Laetin A'Shera£6£After you defend against an attack, if the attack did not hit, you may assign 1 evade token to your ship.££18££4
2800£24£1£Guri£5£At the start of the Combat phase, if you are at Range 1 of an enemy ship, you may assign 1 focus token to your ship.£2,4£30££4
2801£24£0£Black Sun Vigo£3£Following the success of the Virago prototype, the StarViper-class attack platform was streamlined and redesigned for mass production.£4£27££4
2802£24£0£Black Sun Enforcer£1£Prince Xizor himself collaborated with MandalMotors to design the StarViper-class attack platform, one of the most formidable starfighters in the galaxy.£4£25££4
2803£24£1£Prince Xizor£7£When defending, a friendly ship at Range 1 may suffer 1 uncancelled hit or critical result instead of you.£2,4£31££4
2900£38£1£Kavil£7£When attacking a ship outside your firing arc, roll 1 additional attack die.£2,7,4,4,10£24££4
2901£38£0£Hired Gun£4£Just the mention of Imperial credits can bring a host of less than trust worthy individuals to your side.£7,4,4,10£20££4
2902£38£1£Drea Renthal£5£After you spend a target lock, you may receive 1 stress token to acquire a target lock.£7,4,4,10£22££4
2903£38£0£Syndicate Thug£2£Though far from nimble, the Y-wing's heavy hull, substantial shielding, and turret-mounted cannons make them excellent patrol craft.£7,4,4,10£18££4
3000£41£0£Trandoshan Slaver£2£The spacious triple-decker design of the YV-666 made it popular among bounty hunters and slavers, who often retrofitted an entire deck for prisoner transport.£6,5,9,9,9,14£29££4
3001£41£1£Latts Razzi£5£When a friendly ship declares an attack, you may spend a target lock you have on the defender to reduce its agility by 1 for that attack.£6,5,9,9,9,14£33££4
3002£41£1£Moralo Eval£6£You can perform Cannon secondary weapon attacks against ships inside your auxiliary firing arc.£6,5,9,9,9,14£34££4
3003£41£1£Bossk£7£When you perform an attack that hits, before dealing damage, you may cancel 1 of your critical results to add 2 hit results.£2,6,5,9,9,9,14£35££4
3100£42£1£Kaa'to Leeachos£5£At the start of the Combat phase, you may remove 1 focus or evade token from another friendly ship at Range 1-2 and assign it to yourself.£2,5,14£15££4
3101£42£0£Black Sun Soldier£3£The vast and influential Black Sun crime syndicate can always find a use for talented pilots, provided they aren't particular about how they earn their credits.£5,14£13££4
3102£42£0£Binayre Pirate£1£Operating from the Double Worlds, Talus and Tralus, Kath Scarlet's gang of smugglers and pirates would never be described as reputable or dependable - even by other criminals.£5,14£12££4
3103£42£1£N'dru Suhlak£7£While attacking, if there are no other friendly ships at Range 1-2, roll 1 additional attack die.£2,5,14£17££4
3200£3£1£Norra Wexley£7£When attacking or defending, you may spend a target lock you have on the enemy ship to add 1 Focus result to your roll.£2,4,9,3£29££2
3201£3£1£Shara Bey£6£When another friendly ship at Range 1-2 is attacking, it may treat your blue target lock tokens as its own.£2,4,9,3£28££2
3202£3£1£Thane Kyrell£4£After an enemy ship inside your firing arc at Range 1-3 attacks another friendly ship, you may perform a free action.£4,9,3£26££2
3203£3£1£Braylen Stramm£3£After you execute a maneuver, you may roll an attack die. On a hit or critical result, remove 1 stress token from your ship.£4,9,3£25££2
3300£4£1£"Zeb" Orrelios£3£When defending, you may cancel critical hit results before hit results.£7,9£18££2
3301£4£1£Ezra Bridger£4£When defending, if you are stressed, you may change up to 2 of your focus results to evade results.£2,7,9£20££2
3302£4£1£Hera Syndulla£7£When you reveal a green or red maneuver, you may rotate your dial to another maneuver of the same difficulty.£2,7,9£22££2
3303£4£1£Sabine Wren£5£Immediately before you reveal your maneuver, you may perform a free boost or barrel roll action.£2,7,9£21££2
3400£9£1£Zuckuss£7£When attacking, you may roll 1 additional attack die. If you do, then the defender rolls 1 additional defense die.£2,9,11,14£28££4
3401£9£1£4-LOM£6£At the start of the End phase, you may assign 1 of your stress tokens to another ship at Range 1.£2,9,11,14£27££4
3402£9£0£Gand Findsman£5£The legendary Findsmen of Gand worshipped the enshrouding mists of their home planet. Utilizing signs, augurs, and mystical rituals to track their quarry.£2,9,11,14£25££4
3403£9£0£Ruthless Freelancer£3£Byblos Drive Yards earned a reputation for producing starships of questionable quality, but their willingness to perform modifications of questionable legality kept business brisk.£9,11,14£23££4
3500£17£0£Contracted Scout£3£Built for long-distance reconnaissance and plotting new hyperspace routes, the lightly armed JumpMaster 5000 was often extensively retrofitted with custom upgrades.£2,4,4,9,10,14£25££4
3501£17£1£Dengar£9£Once per round after defending, if the attacker is inside your firing arc, you may perform an attack against that ship.£2,4,4,9,10,14£33££4
3502£17£1£Manaroo£4£At the start of the Combat phase, you may assign all focus, evade, and target lock tokens assigned to you to another friendly ship.£2,4,4,9,10,14£27££4
3503£17£1£Tel Trevura£7£The first time you would be destroyed, instead cancel any remaining damage, discard all Damage cards, and deal 4 facedown Damage cards to this ship.£2,4,4,9,10,14£30££4
3600£22£1£Fenn Rau£9£When attacking or defending, if the enemy ship is at Range 1, you may roll 1 additional dice.£2,4£28££4
3601£22£1£Old Teroch£7£At the start of the Combat phase, you may choose 1 enemy ship at Range 1. If you are inside its firing arc, it discards all focus and evade tokens.£2,4£26££4
3602£22£1£Kad Solus£6£After you execute a red maneuver, assign 2 focus tokens to your ship.£2,4£25££4
3603£22£0£Concord Dawn Ace£5£The elite of the Concord Dawn Protectorate mastered the Concordia Face Off maneuver, leveraging their ships' narrow attack profile to execute deadly head-on charges.£2,4£23££4
3604£22£0£Concord Dawn Veteran£3£Concord Dawn Protectors favored an aggressive approach, using their craft's pivot wing technology to achieve unmatched agility in the pursuit of their quarry.£2,4£22££4
3605£22£0£Zealous Recruit£1£The Concord Dawn Protectorate starfighter was armed with a hidden torpedo launcher, allowing it to launch a deadly salvo before its foes realized it was carrying ordnance.£4,3£20££4
3700£45£1£Ketsu Onyo£7£At the start of the Combat phase, you may choose a ship at Range 1. If it is inside your primary and mobile firing arcs, assign 1 tractor beam token to it.£2,9,14,14£38££4
3701£45£1£Asajj Ventress£6£At the start of the Combat phase, you may choose a ship at Range 1-2. If it is inside your mobile firing arc, assign 1 stress token to it.£2,9,14,14£37££4
3702£45£1£Sabine Wren£5£When defending against an enemy ship inside your mobile firing arc at Range 1-2, you may add 1 Focus result to your roll.£9,14,14£35££4
3703£45£0£Shadowport Hunter£2£Crime syndicates augmented the lethal skills of their loyal contractors with the best weapons, ships, and tech available.£9,14,14£33££4
3800£34£1£"Quickdraw"£9£Once per round, when you lose a shield token, you may perform a primary weapon attack.£2,11,5,18£29££3
3801£34£1£"Backdraft"£7£When attacking a ship inside your auxiliary firing arc, you may add 1 critical result.£2,11,5,18£27££3
3802£34£0£Omega Specialist£5£Special Forces TIE fighters employed a dual heavy laser turret mounted to the bottom of the fuselage to defend against threats from the rear and augment their forward firepower.£2,11,5,18£25££3
3803£34£0£Zeta Specialist£3£Only the most elite pilots of the First Order were authorized to fly this specialized two-seater TIE craft outfitted with enhanced shields, weapons, and sensor systems.£11,5,18£23££3
3900£35£1£Hera Syndulla£7£When you reveal a red or green maneuver, you may rotate your dial to another maneuver of the same difficulty.£11,7,4,4,9,9£40££1
3901£35£1£Kanan Jarrus£5£When an enemy ship at Range 1-2 is attacking, you may spend a focus token. If you do, the attacker rolls 1 fewer attack die.£11,7,4,4,9,9£38££1
3902£35£1£"Chopper"£4£At the start of the Combat phase, each enemy ship you are touching receives 1 stress token.£11,7,4,4,9,9£37££1
3903£35£0£Lothal Rebel£3£Another successful Corellian Engineering Corporation freighter design, the VCX-100 was larger than the ubiquitous YT-series, boasting more living space and customizability.£11,7,4,4,9,9£35££1
4000£47£1£The Inquisitor£8£When attacking with your primary weapon at Range 2-3, treat the range of the attack as Range 1.£2,5£25££3
4001£47£1£Valen Rudor£6£After defending, you may perform a free action.£2,5£22££3
4002£47£0£Baron of the Empire£4£The aristocratic title of baron was presented to ace starfighter pilots for outstanding service to the Empire.£2,5£19££3
4003£47£0£Sienar Test Pilot£2£Sienar Fleet System's TIE Advanced v1 was a groundbreaking starfighter design featuring upgraded engines, a missile launcher, and folding s-foils.£5£16££3
4100£48£1£"Duchess"£8£While you have the 'Adaptive Ailerons' Upgrade card equipped, you may choose to ignore its card ability.£2£23££3
4101£48£1£"Pure Sabacc"£6£When attacking. If you have 1 or fewer Damage cards, roll 1 additional attack die.£2£22££3
4102£48£1£"Countdown"£5£When defending, if you are not stressed during the "Compare Results" step, you may suffer 1 damage to cancel all dice results. if you do, receive 1 stress token.££20££3
4103£48£0£Black Squadron Scout£4£Black Squadron pilots who had proven themselves as highly adept pilots were occassionally issued TIE strikers when sent on atmospheric missions.£2£20££3
4104£48£0£Scarif Defender£3£To protect the secret jungle base, the Empire required a vigilant and swift defense force.££18££3
4105£48£0£Imperial Trainee£1£After the Republic fell and as the Empire rose, the new galactic government required thousands of new pilots to replace the decommissioned clones.££17££3
4200£49£1£Cassian Andor£6£At the start of the Activation phase you may remove 1 stress token from 1 other friendly ship at Range 1-2.£2,11,4,9,9£27££2
4201£49£1£Bodhi Rook£4£When a friendly ship acquires a target lock, that ship can lock onto an enemy ship at Range 1-3 of any friendly ship.£11,4,9,9£25££2
4202£49£1£Heff Tobber£3£After an enemy ship executes a maneuver that causes it to overlap your ship, you may perform a free action.£11,4,9,9£24££2
4203£49£0£Blue Squadron Pathfinder£2£Used for deploying troops under the cover of darkness or into the heat of battle, the U-wing fulfilled the Rebel Alliance's need for a hardy transport craft.£11,4,9,9£23££2
4300£50£1£Constable Zuvio£7£When you reveal a reverse maneuver, you may drop a bomb using your front guides (including a bomb with the "Action:" header).£2,9,8,18,14£19££4
4301£50£1£Sarco Plank£5£When defending instead of using your agility value, you may roll a number of defense dice equal to the speed of the maneuver you executed this round.£2,9,8,18,14£18££4
4302£50£1£Unkar Plutt£3£At the end of the Activation phase you must assign a tractor beam token to each ship you are touching.£9,8,18,14£17££4
4303£50£0£Jakku Gunrunner£1£The Quadrijet transfer spacetug, commonly called a 'Quadjumper,' was nimble in space and atmosphere alike, making it popular among both smugglers and explorers.£9,8,18,14£15££4
4400£51£1£Ahsoka Tano£7£At the start of the Combat phase, you may spend 1 focus token to choose a friendly ship at Range 1. It may perform 1 free action.£2£17££2
4401£51£1£Sabine Wren£5£Immediately before you reveal your maneuver, you may perform a free boost or barrel roll action.£2£15££2
4402£51£1£Captain Rex£4£After you perform an attack, assign the 'Suppressive Fire' Condition card to the defender.££14££2
4403£51£1£Zeb Orrelios£3£When defending, you may cancel [crit] results before [hit] results.££13££2
4500£52£1£Kylo Ren£6£The first time you are hit by an attack each round, assign the "I'll Show You the Dark Side" Condition card to the attacker.£2,11,9,9,18,18£34££3
4501£52£1£Major Stridan£4£For the purpose of your actions and Upgrade cards, you may treat friendly ships at Range 2-3 as being at Range 1.£11,9,9,18,18£32££3
4502£52£1£Lieutenant Dormitz£3£During setup, friendly ships may be placed anywhere in the play area at Range 1-2 of you.£11,9,9,18,18£31££3
4503£52£0£Starkiller Base Pilot£2£The Upsilon-class shuttle served as a command ship for many of the First Order's elite officers and agents as they spread terror across the galaxy.£11,9,9,18,18£30££3